{
    "id": "8d214dd42c9644b39dfb7bc731dfa32c",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Susie ……………………….. a new boyfriend.",
            "description": "Either could be used here. However, the got form of have is more common.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "has got",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. fever last week.",
            "description": "Got forms are not common with had.",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "had got",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… good neighbors when you lived in the city?",
            "description": "Got forms are not common with had.",
            "answers": [
                "Had you got",
                "Did you have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. a toothache.",
            "description": "Progressive forms of have are not normally used with meanings that refer to a state.",
            "answers": [
                "have got",
                "have",
                "am having"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. to work on Sundays.",
            "description": "In negative sentences we use do not have.",
            "answers": [
                "haven't",
                "don't have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly I ………………………. a thud.",
            "description": "We use listen to to talk about paying attention to sounds that are going on.",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "listened to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help me ……………………….. my ring?",
            "description": "The infinitive can be used with or without to after help.",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "to find",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………………. is she?",
            "description": "We use tall for people, trees, buildings etc.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have got lovely ………………………… legs.",
            "description": "Parts of the body can be long, not tall.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "long",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How …………………………. Sundays!",
            "description": "The verb comes after the subject in exclamations.",
            "answers": [
                "I love",
                "do I love"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………………….. grown!",
            "description": "The verb comes after the subject in exclamations.",
            "answers": [
                "have you",
                "you have",
                "do you have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Stir well ………………………. I do.",
            "description": "In comparisons we use as, like or the way. We don’t use how.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "the way",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}